{
    "subject": "resource/The_Birthday_Party_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/Max_Rosenberg",
    "human_readable": "The producer of The Birthday Party (film) is Max Rosenberg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.943263053894043,
            "question": "Is Max Rosenberg a film producer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9211422204971313,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Max Rosenberg."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.912600576877594,
            "question": "Max Rosenberg is known for producing which film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8942160606384277,
            "question": "Who produced the film 'The Birthday Party'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8566415905952454,
            "question": "What type of work did Max Rosenberg do on 'The Birthday Party'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8011065721511841,
            "question": "What is the name of the producer of 'The Birthday Party'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7033010125160217,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the production of 'The Birthday Party'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6494590640068054,
            "question": "Who directed 'The Birthday Party'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6083375811576843,
            "question": "What other films has Max Rosenberg worked on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5000029802322388,
            "question": "What year was 'The Birthday Party' released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of The Birthday Party (film) is Max Rosenberg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2969_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other films has Max Rosenberg worked on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2969_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed 'The Birthday Party'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2969_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the production of 'The Birthday Party'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2969_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2969_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2969_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2969_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2969_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2969_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2969_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2969_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2969_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2969_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2969_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that the documents mention Max J. Rosenberg as a film producer who worked on various films, including horror or supernatural films, and was involved in the production of Amicus productions. However, there is no explicit mention of him being associated with the specific film \"The Birthday Party (1968)\".\n\nTherefore, my evaluation is:\n\n{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Max J. Rosenberg was a film producer, and they mention his production of \"The Birthday Party\" in 1968, which aligns with the query about him being the producer of The Birthday Party (film)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "One of the films Rosenberg was most proud of was his 1968 version of Harold Pinter\u2019s The Birthday Party, which starred Robert Shaw, and was directed by William Friedkin.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}